Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Addition, 2004 [A2004-19] (Box 60)
  - Faculty and staff (Box 60)
    - Landon, Charles E. (Box 82)
    - Lange, David L. [Law] (Box 82)
    - Lange, Peter [Political Science] (Box 82)
    - Lange, Peter, 1995- (Box 82)
    - Langley, J. H. (Box 82)
    - Langford, Thomas A. [Methodist Studies], Pre-1980 (Box 82)
    - Langford, Thomas A. [Methodist Studies], Post-1980 (Box 82)
    - LaRocca-Pitts, Elizabeth [Divinity] (Box 82)
    - LaRoe, Rachel (Box 82)
    - Larson, David [Psychiatry] (Box 82)
    - Lassaw, Ibram (Box 82)
    - Laszlo, John [Hematology and Medicine] (Box 82)
    - Lattimore, Caroline L. [Minority Affairs] (Box 82)
    - Laughhunn, Danny J. [Fuqua Business] (Box 82)
    - Laurie, Cathy C. [Zoology] (Box 82)
    - Laursen, Tod A., 1993 (Box 82)
    - Lavine, Michael L. [Institute of Statistics and Decision Sciences, the Environment] (Box 82)
    - Law, James Roland (Box 82)
    - Lawing, William Dennis, Jr. (Box 82)
    - Lawler, Gregory F. [Mathematics] (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, Bruce B. [Religion Dept.] (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, Bruce B. [Religion Dept.], 1994- (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, Bruce B. [Religion Dept.], 2001 (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, Keith S. [News Service] (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, Keith S. [News Service], 2001 (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, Patricia A. (Box 82)
    - Lawrence, William B. [Divinity School] (Box 82)
    - Lawson, Dewey [Physics] (Box 82)
    - Lawson, Dunbar (Box 82)
    - Layton, Harold Erick [Department of Mathematics] (Box 82)
    - Layton, Philip Raymond (Box 82)
    - Leach, Richard H. [Political Science] (Box 82)
    - Leary, Lewis (Box 82)
    - LeBar, John A. [Health, Physical Education and Recreation] (Box 82)
    - Lecky, Hugh (Box 82)
    - LeCompagnon, Betty (Box 82)
    - Ledbetter, Freedman [Pharmacologist], 29737 (Box 82)
    - Lee, Howard, 1966-1976 (Box 82)
    - Lee, Kerry L. [Biometry and Med. Informatics Div., Dept. CandF Med.] (Box 82)
    - Lee, Lillian Armfield, Retired 5-31-1986 (Box 82)
    - Lee, Luke Tsung-Chou (Box 82)
    - Lee, Paul P. [Ophthalmology] (Box 82)
    - Lees, Jack A. [Mathematics], Aptd Sept 1971, Retired 5-31-1986 (Box 82)
    - Lefkowitz, Robert J. [Cardiology, Medicine, Biochemistry] (Box 82)
    - Lefkowitz, Robert J. [Cardiology, Medicine, Biochemistry], 1995- (Box 82)
    - Lefkowitz, Robert J. [Cardiology, Medicine, Biochemistry], 2001 (Box 82)
    - Lefler, Wes (Box 82)
    - Lefurgey, Ann [Physiology] (Box 82)
    - Leight, George S., Jr. [Gen/Thoraic Surgery, Surgery] (Box 82)
    - Leighten, Patricia [Art and Art History] (Box 82)
    - Leitzel, Jim [Public Policy] (Box 82)
    - Lentricchia, Frank [English] (Box 82)
    - Lentricchia, Melissa (Box 82)
    - Leonard, Henry S. (Box 82)
    - Leonard, Larry (Box 82)
    - Leone, Bruce J. [Anesthesiology, CPR Lab] (Box 82)
    - Lerner, Gerda (Box 82)
    - Lerner, Warren [History] (Box 82)
    - Leshin, Richard (Box 82)
    - LeSourd, Howard Marion (Box 82)
    - Lester, D. W. (Box 82)
    - Lester, Richard Allen (Box 82)
    - Lester, Richard G. (Box 82)
    - Lever, Oscar William (Box 82)
    - Levin, Betsy [Law] (Box 82)
    - Levin, Edward D. [Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences] (Box 82)
    - Levin, Lawrence Schott [Surgery], 2001 (Box 82)
    - Levinson, Judith Charlotte [English Dept.], 25082 (Box 82)
    - Lewin, Arie Y. [Fuqua Business] (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Harold G. [Economics] (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Harold W. [Physics] (Box 82)
    - Lewis, John B. (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Leroy (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Ralph E. (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Susan [Law] (Box 82)
    - Leydon, Betty (Box 82)
    - Li, Wei [Fuqua Business] (Box 82)
    - Liacouras, Peter G. (Box 82)
    - Liddle, Rodger (Box 82)
    - Lieberman, Melvyn [Physiology] (Box 82)
    - Liebmann, Emil (Box 82)
    - Liebowitz, Harold [Religion Dept.], 1972-73 (Box 82)
    - Liebowite, Richard (Box 82)
    - Lievsay, John L. [English Dept.] (Box 82)
    - Lin, Haifan [Cell Biology] (Box 82)
    - Lin, Nan [Sociology Dept., Asian/Pacific Studies] (Box 82)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion], Pre-1980 (Box 83)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion], thru 1987 (Box 83)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion], 1989-90 (Box 83)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion], 1991-92 (Box 83)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion], 1993 (Box 83)
    - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion], 1994- (Box 83)
    - Lind, Allan [Fuqua Business] (Box 83)
    - Lind, Marcia [Philosophy] (Box 83)
    - Lindahl, Frederick [Business Administration] (Box 83)
    - Linderoth, L. Sigfred, Jr., Sept. 1, 1965 (Box 83)
    - Lindsay, Dale R. [Medical and Allied Health Education] (Box 83)
    - Linebarger, Paul M. A. (Box 83)
    - Lingenheld, Edward C. [Admissions] (Box 83)
    - Linke, William R. (Box 83)
    - Linney, Elwood [Microbiology, Pharmacology] (Box 83)
    - Lippard, Nancy (Box 83)
    - Lipper, Steve [Biological Psychology] (Box 83)
    - Lipscomb, J. Walton (Box 83)
    - Lipscomb, Joseph, Jr. [Inst. Of Policy Science, Dept. CandF Med.] (Box 83)
    - Lischer, Richard [Divinity School] (Box 83)
    - Lisowski, Paul William [Physics], 1974- (Box 83)
    - Lister-Sink, Barbara [Music], 1975-76 (Box 83)
    - Little, James (Box 83)
    - Littman, Michael [Computer Science] (Box 83)
    - Litvinenko, Vladimir [Physics] (Box 83)
    - Litzinger, Ralph A. [Cultural Anthropology] (Box 83)
    - Livengood, Charles III [Gynecology; Chlamydia Lab] (Box 83)
    - Livesay, John Leon (Box 83)
    - Livingston, Elizabeth [Mtrnl/Fetal] (Box 83)
    - Livingstone, Daniel A. [Zoology], Pre-1980 (Box 83)
    - Livingstone, Daniel A. [Zoology], Post-1980 (Box 83)
    - Llewellyn, Charles E., Jr. [Student Mental Health Service], Retired March 2, 1987 (Box 83)
    - Lloyd, Douglas S. (Box 83)
    - Lloyd, Jane (Box 83)
    - Lo, Donald C. [Neurobiology] (Box 83)
    - Lober, Douglas [Environment] (Box 83)
    - Lobo, Miguel [Fuqua Business], 2001 (Box 83)
    - Lochbaum, Ronald (Box 83)
    - Lcohmuller, Charles H. [Chemistry, Biomedical Engineering] (Box 83)
    - Lochman, John E. [Psychiatry, Psychology] (Box 83)
    - Locke, Elizabeth (Betsy) [Office of Publications] (Box 84)
    - Lockhead, Gregory Roger [Psychology] (Box 84)
    - Lodge, George Townsend (Box 84)
    - Loendorf, David (Box 84)
    - Logan, Barry Lee (Box 84)
    - Lohner, Christian M. (Box 84)
    - Lomperis, Timothy J. [Political Science] (Box 84)
    - London, Arthur H. (Box 84)
    - London, Edith (Box 84)
    - London, Fritz (Frederick) (Box 84)
    - Long, Croft (Box 84)
    - Long, Eugene Thomas [Philosophy], 1968-69 (Box 84)
    - Long, Stephen [Divinity] (Box 84)
    - Long, Stephen [Divinity], 1993 (Box 84)
    - Longino, Michele [Romance Studies] (Box 84)
    - Looney, Jacqueline [Graduate School], 2001 (Box 84)
    - Looney, John G. [Child and Adolescent Psychiatry] (Box 84)
    - Loos, James S. [Physics] (Box 84)
    - Love, Randall M. [Music] (Box 84)
    - Loveland, Donald W. [Computer Science ] (Box 84)
    - Lowe, James E. [Gen/Thoraic Surgery, Pathology] (Box 84)
    - Lowe, Ruth H. (Box 84)
    - Lowenbach, Hans [Psychiatry, Pediatrics], 10-19-83, Retired 8-31-74 (Box 84)
    - Lowman, Rodney L. [Medical Psychology] (Box 84)
    - Lowndes, Charles L. B. (Box 84)
    - Lubans, John, Jr. [Information Services] (Box 84)
    - Lucas, John Paul (Box 84)
    - Lucas, Peter W. [Physics] (Box 84)
    - Luken, Ellen [Medical Alumni Affairs] (Box 84)
    - Luken, William L., Jr. [Chemistry], Prof 9-1-76; Retired 8-31-83 (Box 84)
    - Lumb, Philip D. [Anesthesiology; Surgery] (Box 84)
    - Lund, John J. (Box 84)
    - Lundberg, John G. [Zoology] (Box 84)
    - Luney, Percy R. [Law] (Box 84)
    - Lupton, Jane (Box 84)
    - Luttrell, Wendy (Box 84)
    - Luvaas, Morten Jay (Box 84)
    - Lyerly, Kim [Gen. and Thor. Surgery; Pathology; Immunology; Gen and Cell Therapy] (Box 84)
    - Lyles, Kenneth W. [Geriatrics; Metabolism, Endocrinology and Genetics] (Box 84)
    - Lynch, George Cuninggin (Box 84)
    - Lynch, John G., Jr. [Fuqua Business] (Box 84)
    - Lynch, Thomas [Psychology], 1999 (Box 84)
    - Lynn, George Edward (Box 84)
    - Lynn, William S. [Biochemistry and Medicine] (Box 84)
    - Lynts, George W. [Geology Department] (Box 84)
    - Macduff, John N. [Mechanical Engineering], Retired 8-31-78 (Box 84)
    - Mace, Robert (Box 84)
    - MacFall, James [Radiology] (Box 84)
    - Machemer, Robert [Opthamology] (Box 84)
    - MacIntyre, Alasdair [Philosophy] (Box 84)
    - MacIntyre, Neil R. [Pulmonary Medicine; Respiratory Care Services] (Box 84)
    - MacPhail, Richard [Chemistry] (Box 84)
    - MacPhee, Ross D. [Anatomy] (Box 84)
    - Madden, David J. [Medical Psychology] (Box 84)
    - Maddox, George L. [Department of Sociology] (Box 84)
    - Madey, John [Physics; FEL Laboratory] (Box 85)
    - Madison, Roger [Neurosurgery; Surgery] (Box 85)
    - Magat, Wesley A. "Wes" [Fuqua Business; Public Policy Studies] (Box 85)
    - Magat, Wesley A. "Wes" [Fuqua Business; Public Policy Studies], d. 3/1999 (Box 85)
    - Magid, Alan D. [Physiology] (Box 85)
    - Magruder-Habib, Kathryn [Biometry and Med; Informatics; CandF Medicine] (Box 85)
    - Maguire, Lynn A. [Forestry ] (Box 85)
    - Maguire, Robert (Box 85)
    - Mahaffey, Kenneth [Cardiology] (Box 85)
    - Mahaffey, Samuel M. [Pediatric Surgery] (Box 85)
    - Mahaley, Moses S. (Box 85)
    - Maheshwary, Avinash C. [Librarian; Bibliographer; South Asia/ Middle East Collection Development Dept.] (Box 85)
    - Mahoney, Edward P. [Philosophy] (Box 85)
    - Maier, Steven F. [Fuqua Business] (Box 85)
    - Malin, Peter [Nicholas School; Civil and Envir. Engineering] (Box 85)
    - Malone, Bill C., 1999 (Box 85)
    - Malouf, Melissa [English] (Box 85)
    - Malson, Micheline [Public Policy] (Box 85)
    - Maltbie, Allan A. [Psychiatry] (Box 85)
    - Mandel, Lazaro J. [Physiology] (Box 85)
    - Mandl, Michael J. [Financial Services] (Box 85)
    - Mann, Everett J. (Box 85)
    - Mann, W. Joseph [Continuing Education; Divinity School] (Box 85)
    - Manton, Kenneth G. [Community and Family Medicine], Before 1993 (Box 85)
    - Manton, Kenneth G. [Community and Family Medicine], 1993 (Box 85)
    - Manton, Kenneth G. [Community and Family Medicine], 1994- (Box 85)
    - Manton, Kenneth G. [Community and Family Medicine], 2001 (Box 85)
    - March, John S. [Child and Adol. Psychiatry] (Box 85)
    - Marchase, Richard B. [Medical Research; Anatomy] (Box 85)
    - Marchuk, Douglas A. [Genetics] (Box 85)
    - Marinos, Peter N. [Graduate Studies; Electrial Engineering] (Box 85)
    - Mark, Daniel [Cardiology ] (Box 85)
    - Markert, M. Louise [Allergy and Immunology; Pediatrics] (Box 85)
    - Markley, Robert F. [Corporate/Foundation Relations; Research Administration] (Box 85)
    - Markman, Sidney, retired Aug. 31, 1981 (Box 85)
    - Marks, Jeffrey R., 2001 (Box 85)
    - Marks, Lawrence [Radiation Oncology], 1999 (Box 85)
    - Marler, George Eric (Box 85)
    - Marsden, George M. [Divinity School] (Box 85)
    - Marsh, Gail R. [Medical Psychology; Psychology] (Box 85)
    - Marshall, Lynn La Due (Box 85)
    - Marshall, Norman (Box 85)
    - Marshall, Robert C. [Economics] (Box 85)
    - Marshall, Roger L., Sec. of the University eff. July 1, 1986 (Box 85)
    - Martin, Abram V., Jr. (Box 85)
    - Martin, Anne L. [Health Administration] (Box 85)
    - Martin, Dale B. [Religion Dept.] (Box 85)
    - Martin, David Vance [Education] (Box 85)
    - Martin, Donald S. (Box 85)
    - Martin, Jean (Box 85)
    - Martin, Mrs. John H. (Elsie Wilson) (Box 85)
    - Martin, Joseph B. III (Box 85)
    - Martin, Paul [DUMC], 1998 (Box 85)
    - Martin, Ruth (Box 85)
    - Martin, Samuel P. (Box 85)
    - Martin, Shirley (Box 85)
    - Martin, Willard Edgar, Jr. (Box 85)
    - Martin, William Francis (Box 85)
    - Martinez, Salutario [Imaging; Radiology] (Box 85)
    - Mason, Robert [Orthodontics; Surgery] (Box 85)
    - Mass, Peter (Box 85)
    - Massanari, Ronald L [Divinity School] (Box 85)
    - Massey, Edward Wayne [Neurology] (Box 85)
    - Massoud, Hisham Z. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 85)
    - Matchar, David B. [General Medicine; Center for Health Policy Research and Education] (Box 85)
    - Matheson, C.R. (Box 85)
    - Mathew, Roy T. [Psychiatry] (Box 85)
    - Mathews, Donald C. (Box 85)
    - Mathews, George, Jr. (Box 85)
    - Matte, Ignacio Elanco (Box 85)
    - Matthew, William D. [Neurobiology] (Box 85)
    - Matthews, L. T. (Box 85)
    - Matthews, Martha (Box 85)
    - Matthias, Anne Powell (Mrs. Robert C.) (Box 85)
    - Mattingly, Capitola (Box 85)
    - Mau, James (Box 85)
    - Maug, Ernst (Box 85)
    - Maughan, William (Box 85)
    - Mauskopf, Seymour [Graduate Studies; History] (Box 85)
    - Maves, David Walter [Music], 1972- (Box 85)
    - Maxfield, Joseph Pease (Box 85)
    - Maxwell, Richard C. [Law], retired Feb. 24, 1989 (Box 85)
    - May, Carolyn, 1980 (Box 85)
    - May, David E. (Box 85)
    - May, George (Box 85)
    - Mayer, Frederick [Inst. of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs] (Box 85)
    - Mayer, Frederick [Inst. of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs], 2001 (Box 85)
    - Mayfield, Demmie G. [Psychiatry] (Box 86)
    - Mayfield, Henry D. (Box 86)
    - Mayfield, Marie Marcia (Box 86)
    - Maynard, Hubbard D., retired, 8-31-85 (Box 86)
    - Mazumdar, Sucheta [History], 2001 (Box 86)
    - Mazzola, Joseph [Fuqua Business] (Box 86)
    - McAdams, Page [Radiology], 1998 (Box 86)
    - McAlister, Florence (Box 86)
    - McAlister, Joe (Box 86)
    - McAuley, Gloria M. [Employee Services; Human Resources] (Box 86)
    - McAuliffe, Johanna [Drama Dept.] (Box 86)
    - McBride, Colleen [Comm. and Family Medicine] (Box 86)
    - McBryde, John M., Jr. (Box 86)
    - McCall, Adeline (Box 86)
    - McCann, John [Fuqua Business] (Box 86)
    - McCann, Richard L. [Gen and Thoracic Surgery] (Box 86)
    - McCants, Thomas (Box 86)
    - McCardle, Kevin F. [Business Administration] (Box 86)
    - McCarroll, Earl (Box 86)
    - McCarthy, Gregory [Radiology] (Box 86)
    - McCarty, Kenneth, Jr. [Pathology; Medicine] (Box 86)
    - McCarty, Kenneth S., Sr. [Biochemistry] (Box 86)
    - McCaughan, Ralph L. [University Counsel for Development - Office of the University Counsel] (Box 86)
    - McCauley, C. Edward [Duke Hospital], Associate Director, 1969-71 (Box 86)
    - McClay, David R. [Zoology] (Box 86)
    - McClellan, John (Box 86)
    - McCloy, Shelby T. (Box 86)
    - McClure, Wallace (Box 86)
    - McCollough, Thomas Elmore [Religion], pre-1995 (Box 86)
    - McCollough, Thomas Elmore [Religion], 1995- (Box 86)
    - McCollum, David E. [Orthopaedic Surgery; Surgery] (Box 86)
    - McColm, Mary (Box 86)
    - McCombs, Arthur A. (Box 86)
    - McConahay, John B. [Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs], 1976-77 (Box 86)
    - McConahay, John B. [Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs], 1978-94 (Box 86)
    - McConahay, John B. [Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs], 1995-98 (Box 86)
    - McConville, Robert H., Jr. [Comm. and Family Medicine] (Box 86)
    - McCormack, William Charles (Box 86)
    - McCormick, Claudia (Box 86)
    - McCormick, John C. (Box 86)
    - McCracken, Maude (Box 86)
    - McCrea, Alice [Radiation Therapy] (Box 86)
    - McCrory, Douglas C. [General Medicine ] (Box 86)
    - McCue, Betty F., 1964- (Box 86)
    - McCuen, Brooks W. II [Opatamology] (Box 86)
    - McCulloch, T. L. (Box 86)
    - McCurdy, Linda M. [Perkins Library] (Box 86)
    - McCutcheon, Frederick Harold (Box 86)
    - McDonald, Alexander D. (Box 86)
    - McDonald, Eugene J. [Executive Vice President and University Counsel] (Box 86)
    - McDonald, Marie [Med Genetics; Peds.] (Box 86)
    - McDonald, Patrick H., Sr. (Box 86)
    - McDonnell, Donald [Pharmacology and Cell Biology] (Box 86)
    - McDonnell, Thomas E. [N.R.O.T.C.] (Box 86)
    - McDougall, William (Box 86)
    - McElhaney, Harold (Box 86)
    - McElhaney, James H. [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 86)
    - McElhaney, James W. (Box 86)
    - McElveen, John T., Jr. [Otolaryngology] (Box 86)
    - McElroy, Marjorie B. [Economics] (Box 86)
    - McEvoy, Joseph [Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences] (Box 86)
    - McFalls, Frederick Dunham [Anatomy] (Box 86)
    - McFarland, James A. (Box 86)
    - McGee, John S. (Box 86)
    - McGee, Mike (Box 86)
    - McGinty, Bernard [Medical Center Financial Management] (Box 86)
    - McGough, William E. (Box 86)
    - McGovern, Francis [Law] (Box 86)
    - McGown, Linda B. [Chemistry] (Box 86)
    - McGrath, Daniel F. (Box 86)
    - McGuire, Betty (Box 86)
    - McHeyzer-Williams, Michael G. (Box 86)
    - McHugh, Gelolo [Psychology] (Box 86)
    - McIntosh, Henry (Box 86)
    - McIntosh, Thomas [Cell Biology] (Box 86)
    - McKean, Margaret A. [Political Science] (Box 86)
    - McKeel, James T., Jr. (Box 86)
    - McKenzie, Lionel (Box 86)
    - McKinney, Ross E. [Infectious Diseases, Pediatrics] (Box 86)
    - McKiver, Willard (Box 86)
    - McLachlan, Helen (Box 86)
    - McLawhorn, Ruby (Box 86)
    - McLelland, Robert [Radiology] (Box 86)
    - McLendon, Jonathon C. (Box 86)
    - McLeod, Michael E. [Gastroenterology; Medicine] (Box 86)
    - McLeod, Robert M. (Box 86)
    - McLoyd, Vonnie C. [Psychology] (Box 86)
    - McMahon, John Alexander [Health Administration] (Box 86)
    - McMahon, Samuel M. (Box 86)
    - McManus, Thomas J. [Physiology] (Box 86)
    - McMatton, Timothy (Box 86)
    - McNamara, James O., Sr. [Neurology; Pharmacology] (Box 86)
    - McNeill, John Thomas (Box 86)
    - McNurlen, Lewis J. (Box 86)
    - McPhail, Andrew T. [Chemistry] (Box 86)
    - McPherson, Harry T. [Endocrinology] (Box 86)
    - Meador, Keith G. [Psychiatry] (Box 86)
    - Means, Anthony R. [Pharmacology; Molecular Cancer Biology Dept. in Cancer Center] (Box 86)
    - Meck, Warren H. [Psychology - Experimental] (Box 86)
    - Medina, Miguel A. [Civil Engineering] (Box 87)
    - Meeks, M. Douglas (Box 87)
    - Meliones, Jon N. [Pediatrics] (Box 87)
    - Mellown, Elgin Wendell, Jr. [English] (Box 87)
    - Melosh, Robert J. [Civil Engineering] (Box 87)
    - Mendell, Nancy Role [Medical Research ] (Box 87)
    - Mendoza, Enrique [Economics], 2001 (Box 87)
    - Mengel, Charles E. (Box 87)
    - Meredith, Dennis [Office of Research Communications] (Box 87)
    - Meredith, Jill [Curator] (Box 87)
    - Meriam, James Lathrop (Box 87)
    - Merritt, Gertrude [Faculty of the Arts and Sciences] (Box 87)
    - Metzgar, Richard S. [Microbiology and Immunology] (Box 87)
    - Metzloff, Thomas B. [Law] (Box 87)
    - Meurer, Mike (Box 87)
    - Meyer, Francis P. (Box 87)
    - Meyer, Horst [Physics] (Box 87)
    - Meyers, Carol [Religion] (Box 87)
    - Meyers, Eric M. [Religion] (Box 87)
    - Meyers, William C. [General and Thoracic Surgery] (Box 87)
    - Mezzatesta, Michael P. [Duke University Museum of Art] (Box 88)
    - Mezzatesta, Michael P. [Duke University Museum of Art], 1993- (Box 88)
    - Michener, J. Lloyd [Family Medicine], 1994- (Box 88)
    - Mickey, H. C. (Box 88)
    - Mickey, Paul A. [Divinity School] (Box 88)
    - Mickiewicz, Ellen [Public Policy] (Box 88)
    - Mickle, Thomas P. [Athletics] (Box 88)
    - Miglerese, Sam [Community Affairs] (Box 88)
    - Mignolo, Walter [Romance Studies] (Box 88)
    - Miller, Charles Henderson (Box 88)
    - Miller, David L. [Fuqua Business] (Box 88)
    - Miller, Gustavus H. [Romance Languages] (Box 88)
    - Miller, Kay [Office of University Relations; Medical Center Public Relations] (Box 88)
    - Miller, Lawrence J. [Duke Press] (Box 88)
    - Miller, Martin A. [History; Eastern European/Soviet Studies] (Box 88)
    - Miller, Ylana [History], 2001 (Box 88)
    - Mills, Elliot [Physiology, Pharmacology] (Box 88)
    - Mimms, Christine (Box 88)
    - Minah, Theodore H. (Box 88)
    - Minniear, Wilma A., retired 5-1-84 (Box 88)
    - Miralles, Diego [Infectious Diseases] (Box 88)
    - Mishler, Brent [Botany] (Box 88)
    - Mitcham, C. L. (Box 88)
    - Mitchell, Fannie Y. (Box 88)
    - Mitchell, Thomas Greenfield [Microbiology and Immunology; Clinical Mycology Laboratory] (Box 88)
    - Mitchell, Will [Fuqua Business], 2001 (Box 88)
    - Mitchell, William J. (Box 88)
    - Mock, Geoffrey, 2001 (Box 88)
    - Modrich, Paul L. [Biochemistry] (Box 88)
    - Moeller, Robert C. (Box 88)
    - Moi, Toril [Literature Program] (Box 88)
    - Molter, Jeffrey L. [Medical Center News Office] (Box 88)
    - Moltmann, D. Jurgen (Box 88)
    - Mommaerts, Wilfred F. M. H. (Box 88)
    - Moneta, Larry [Student Affairs] (Box 88)
    - Montana, Gustavo S. [Radiation Oncology] (Box 88)
    - Monsman, Gerald C. [English Dept.], 31533 (Box 88)
    - Moody, James D. (Box 88)
    - Moon, Michael [English Dept.] (Box 88)
    - Moon, Richard E. [Anesthesiology ] (Box 88)
    - Moon, Richard E. [Anesthesiology ], 2001 (Box 88)
    - Moore, Charles A. (Box 88)
    - Moore, Donald T. [Obstetrics and Gynecology] (Box 88)
    - Moore, John Meredith (Box 88)
    - Moore, John W. [Physiology], 1-1-90 (Box 88)
    - Moore, Joseph O. [Hematology and Medical Oncology] (Box 88)
    - Moore, Lawrence C. [Mathematics] (Box 88)
    - Moore, Michael, 1992-93 (Box 88)
    - Moore, William H. [English Dept.] (Box 88)
    - Moorman, Christine [Fuqua Business], 2001 (Box 88)
    - Moorman, Claude T. III [Sports Medicine] (Box 88)
    - Moosa, Ebrahim [Religion] (Box 88)
    - Moosa, Ebrahim [Religion], 2001 (Box 88)
    - Mordan, Mary Jane (Box 88)
    - Mordecai, Samuel Fox (Box 88)
    - Moreiras, Alberto [Romance Studies] (Box 88)
    - Morgan, George Allen, Jr. (Box 88)
    - Morgan, Henry (Box 88)
    - Morgan, J. E. (Box 88)
    - Morgan, Philip [Sociology Dept. ] (Box 88)
    - Morgan, Ruby (Box 88)
    - Morgenstern, Scott [Political Science] (Box 88)
    - Morris, Kenneth C. [Health System, Financial Officer] (Box 88)
    - Morris, Madeline [Law] (Box 88)
    - Morris, Mary Ann [Endocrinology] (Box 88)
    - Morrison, Ashton Byrom (Box 88)
    - Morrison, Clarence L. [USMC] (Box 88)
    - Morrison, David R. [Mathematics and Physics] (Box 88)
    - Morton, Michael M. [Germanic Language and Literature] (Box 88)
    - Moses, Elizabeth (Box 88)
    - Moses, Michael [English Dept.] (Box 88)
    - Moses, Montrose J. [Anatomy, Cell Biology] (Box 88)
    - Mosley, Albert (Box 88)
    - Moss, Florence (Box 88)
    - Mosteller, Robert Paul [Law] (Box 88)
    - Moulin, Herve J. [Economics] (Box 88)
    - Mouzon, James Carlisle [Physics] (Box 88)
    - Moylan, Joseph A., Jr. (Box 88)
    - Mudimbe, Valentin [Romance Languages] (Box 88)
    - Mueller, Berndt [Physics] (Box 88)
    - Mueller, Julia (Box 88)
    - Muenzinger, Karl F. (Box 88)
    - Muga, Bruce J. (Box 88)
    - Muhlbaier, Lawrence H. [Biometry and Medical Informatics; Database for Cardiovascular Diseases] (Box 88)
    - Muller, Berndt [Physics] (Box 88)
    - Munger, Michael [Political Science] (Box 88)
    - Munson, Bruce (Box 88)
    - Munyan, Merrill Calvin (Box 88)
    - Murch, Arvin W. [Sociology Dept. ], 1969- (Box 88)
    - Murphy, Roland [Divinity School] (Box 88)
    - Murray, Brad (Box 88)
    - Murray, F. J., retired 8-31-80 (Box 88)
    - Murray, James Christopher (Box 88)
    - Murray, John Carroll [Dermatology] (Box 89)
    - Musser, Marc J. [Veterans Administration] (Box 89)
    - Musser, A. Wendell (Box 89)
    - Mutch, David G., 1985 (Box 89)
    - Muti, Lorenzo [Music], 1994-96 (Box 89)
    - Myatt, S. W. (Box 89)
    - Myers, Barry S. [Biomed Engineering/Orthopaedic Surgery] (Box 89)
    - Myers, Barry S. [Biomed Engineering/Orthopaedic Surgery], 2001 (Box 89)
    - Myers, Carol (Box 89)
    - Myers, George [Demographic Studies] (Box 89)
    - Myers, Hiram E. (Box 89)
    - Myers, Jack D. (Box 89)
    - Myers, Laurie (Box 89)
    - Myers, Lawrence Edward [Comm. and Family Medicine] (Box 89)
    - Nace, George William (Box 89)